Finding Aid of the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology Records, 1923-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1923-2015, UWM Manuscript Collection 139; 257.9 cubic ft. (741 boxes) 40 binders 1 oversize folder 30,895 digital files (79.5 GB) 1 film reel 4 safety film negatives
  - 5. Related Organizations, 1947-2008
    - American Association of Medical Society Executives, 1987 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - American Association of Retired Persons, 1987 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - American Board of Allergy and Immunology
      - 1970-1976 (Box 446, Folder 7-8)
      - 1976-1987 (Box 174, Folder 7-8)
      - 1988-1993 (Box 256, Folder 1-6)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 174, Folder 9)
      - 1995-1997 (Box 675, Folder 1-3)
      - Liaison Meeting, Tuscon AZ, 1997 June (Box 675, Folder 4)
      - 1998-2000 (Box 675, Folder 5)
      - The American Board of Allergy and Immunology: The First Twenty- Five Years, 1997(?) (Box 377, Folder 2)
      - Analysis for Literature Review for the American Board of Allergy and Immunology Exam, 1997 (Box 493, Folder 2)
      - Board Review, 1987-1995 (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - Literature Review, Pamphlets, 1992-1993, 1995, 1997, 1999, 2001 (Box 430, Folder 65)
      - Nominations to Board, 1976-1995 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - Self-Assessment Program, 1976-1983 (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Syllabus for Literature Review for the American Board of Allergy and Immunology Exam, 1997 (Box 493, Folder 1)
    - American Board of Internal Medicine, 1989-1992 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - American Board of Medical Specialties, 1977-1995 (Box 175, Folder 4-5)
    - American Board of Physician Assistants, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - American College of Allergists
      - 1962-1983 (Box 175, Folder 7-8)
      - 1984-1986 (Box 256, Folder 7-9)
      - 1985 (Box 175, Folder 9)
      - 1986 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - 1987 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - American College of Allergists/American Academy of Allergy and Immunology Negotiating Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - American College of Allergy and Immunology
      - 1988 (Box 176, Folder 2)
      - 1988 (Box 257, Folder 2)
      - 1991-1993 (Box 176, Folder 3-8)
      - 1993-1996 (Box 177, Folder 1-3)
      - White Paper on Merger with AAAI, 1992-1993 (Box 670, Folder 2)
    - American College of Allergy and Immunology/American Academy of Allergy and Immunology
      - Board Review Course, 1985-1993 (Box 177, Folder 4-5)
      - Discussions
        - 1989 (Box 177, Folder 6)
        - 1990 (Box 177, Folder 7-8)
        - 1990 (Box 178, Folder 1-3)
      - Joint Task Force on Practice Parameters
        - undated (Box 178, Folder 4)
        - 1992-1994 (Box 178, Folder 5-6)
        - 1994 (Box 179, Folder 1-2)
      - Negotiating Committee, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 5-7)
      - Outcome Studies, 1993-1995 (Box 179, Folder 8)
      - Task Force on Practice Guidelines, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - American College of Allergy and Immunology
      - Articles of Incorporation and By-Laws, 1991 (Box 446, Folder 9)
      - Guidelines for Family Practice Residents, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - American College of Allergy, Asthma, and Immunology/ American Academy of Allergy, Asthma, and Immunology, Joint Meeting, 2003 (Box 490, Folder 13)
    - American College of Allergy, Asthma, and Immunology/ American Academy of Allergy, Asthma, and Immunology, Joint Task Force on Practice Parameters, 1995 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - American College of Allergy, Asthma, and Immunology, Meeting Highlights, 1997 (Box 465, Folder 15)
    - American College of Cardiology, 1984-1995 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - American College of Chest Physicians, 1991-1994 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - American College of Emergency Physicians, 1983-1994 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - American College of Healthcare Executives, Informational Pamphlet, undated (Box 446, Folder 10)
    - American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, 1990-1991 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - American College of Occupational and Environmental Medicine, 1992-1995 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - American College of Physicians
      - 1987-1993 (Box 180, Folder 6-10)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Clinical Efficacy Assessment Project, 1984-1986 (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 257, Folder 3-6)
      - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 181, Folder 3-5)
      - Medical Knowledge Self-Assessment Program, 1990-1995 (Box 181, Folder 6-7)
      - Medical Knowledge Self-Assessment Program, undated (Box 490, Folder 1)
    - American Congress of Allergy and Immunology
      - Amalgamation Committee, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - Audio-Visual, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Finance Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 182, Folder 3)
      - Ledger, 1976 (Box 438)
      - News Bulletin, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 4)
      - Postgraduate Course Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 5)
      - Program Planning Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 182, Folder 6)
      - Proposed Constitution and By-Laws, 1975-1976 (Box 182, Folder 7)
      - Public Relations Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 182, Folder 8)
      - Scientific Program Committee, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 9)
      - Silbert/McNeil Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 10)
      - Summary of Responsibilities, 1976 (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - American Dental Association
      - 1992 (Box 182, Folder 12)
      - 1998 (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - American Felsol Company, 1960-1961 (Box 446, Folder 11)
    - American Federation for Clinical Research, 1988 (Box 182, Folder 13)
    - American In-Vitro Allergy/Immunology Society, 1989-1992 (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - American Lung Association, 1988-1995 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - American Marketing Association, 1988 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - American Medical Association
      - 1962-1975 (Box 183, Folder 3-4)
      - 1994 (Box 183, Folder 5-7)
      - Access to Care, 1990 (Box 183, Folder 8)
      - Allergy Panel, 1985-1989 (Box 184, Folder 1-2)
      - Allergy Panel, 1987-1989 (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - AMPAC, 1986 (Box 184, Folder 5)
      - Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 184, Folder 6)
      - Antitrust Booklet, 1989 (Box 184, Folder 7)
      - Awards, 1986-1991 (Box 184, Folder 8)
      - Chiropractic Lawsuit, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 9)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence
        - 1985 (Box 184, Folder 11)
        - 1986-1990 (Box 185, Folder 1-7)
        - 1990-1992 (Box 186, Folder 1-7)
        - 1992-1995 (Box 187, Folder 1-6)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 188, Folder 1-3)
      - Council on Legislation, 1985-1986 (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - Council on Medical Services, 1987-1991 (Box 188, Folder 5)
      - Council on Scientific Affairs, 1984-1992 (Box 188, Folder 6-7)
      - Current Procedural Terminology
        - 1980-1993 (Box 188, Folder 8-9)
        - 1994-1995 (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Delineation of Hospital Privileges, 1985 (Box 189, Folder 2)
      - Diagnostic and Therapeutic Technology Assessment Panel, 1986-1990 (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - Digest of National Health Care Use and Expense Indicators, 1987-1988 (Box 189, Folder 4)
      - Drugs, 1984 (Box 189, Folder 5)
      - Dues, 1985-1995 (Box 189, Folder 6)
      - Federal Key Control Grass Roots Lobbying Program, 1985-1994 (Box 189, Folder 7)
      - Federation Consortium, 1994-1995 (Box 189, Folder 8)
      - Health Policy Agenda for the American People, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 9)
      - Health Policy Agenda for the American People, 1988-1989 (Box 189, Folder 10)
      - House of Delegates
        - 1974 (Box 446, Folder 12)
        - 1987 (Box 189, Folder 11)
        - 1988 (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
        - 1989 (Box 190, Folder 3)
        - 1990 (Box 190, Folder 4-5)
        - 1991 (Box 190, Folder 6)
        - 1992 (Box 190, Folder 7-8)
        - 1993 (Box 191, Folder 1-2)
        - 1994 (Box 191, Folder 3-4)
        - 1995 (Box 191, Folder 5)
        - Handbook, 1993 (Box 191, Folder 6-8)
        - Handbook, 1993 (Box 192, Folder 1)
        - Section Council on Allergy
          - 1971-1978 (Box 192, Folder 2-3)
          - 1983-1993 (Box 192, Folder 4)
          - Minutes and Delegates Reports
            - 1965-1979 (Box 192, Folder 5-6)
            - 1980-1990 (Box 193, Folder 1-3)
      - Implications of Tax Law Changes on Professional Dues and Political Contributions, 1986 (Box 193, Folder 4)
      - Journal of the American Medical Association, 1980-1994 (Box 193, Folder 5)
      - Mandatory Medical Assignment, 1988 (Box 193, Folder 6)
      - Market Area Profile Service, 1986 (Box 193, Folder 7)
      - Medical Liability Project, 1993-1995 (Box 193, Folder 8)
      - Medical Malpractice, 1985-1987 (Box 193, Folder 9)
      - Medical Society Relations, 1988-1990 (Box 193, Folder 10)
      - Medicare Physicians Reimbursement, 1987-1991 (Box 193, Folder 11)
      - Membership, 1984-1995 (Box 194, Folder 1-5)
      - National Conference on the Impaired Physician, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 6)
      - Newsweek Supplement, 1985 (Box 194, Folder 7)
      - Parameters Development Survey, 1990-1993 (Box 194, Folder 8)
      - Patient Protection Act, 1994 (Box 194, Folder 9)
      - Physician Office Laboratory Regulations, 1990 (Box 194, Folder 10)
      - Physician Payment Review Commission, 1989 (Box 194, Folder 11)
      - Physicians Manpower, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 12)
      - Physicians' Resource Guide to Health Delivery Systems, 1989 (Box 194, Folder 13)
      - Practice Management, 1994 (Box 194, Folder 14)
      - Presidents' Forum, 1990-1994 (Box 194, Folder 15)
      - Professional Liability, 1989-1990 (Box 194, Folder 16)
      - Publications, 1982-1987 (Box 194, Folder 17)
      - Quick Guide to American Medical Association Services, 1987 (Box 194, Folder 18)
      - Referral Directory, 1995 (Box 446, Folder 13)
      - Regular Use of Inhaled Corticosteroid Reduces Risk of Fatal or Near-Fatal Asthma, 1992 (Box 195, Folder 1)
      - Relative Value Study
        - 1984-1995 (Box 195, Folder 2-9)
        - 1995 (Box 196, Folder 1-3)
      - Residency Review Committee, 1995 (Box 196, Folder 4)
      - Risk Management and Commentaries for the Medical Office, 1990 (Box 196, Folder 5)
      - RUC Advisory Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 196, Folder 6)
      - Session on Allergy, 1947-1964 (Box 196, Folder 7)
      - Section on Allergy, 1965-1969 (Box 196, Folder 8)
      - Section Council on Allergy, 1970 (Box 196, Folder 9)
      - Section Council on Allergy, 1971-1975 (Box 197, Folder 1)
      - Seeking Quality Medical Care and What You Should Know, 1987 (Box 197, Folder 2)
      - Specialty Society Medical Liability Project
        - 1990-1993 (Box 197, Folder 3)
        - Meeting, 1992 (Box 197, Folder 4-6)
      - Task Force on Professional Liability and Insurance
        - 1986-1987 (Box 197, Folder 7-9)
        - 1987-1988 (Box 198, Folder 1-2)
      - Telephone Directory, 1989-1990 (Box 198, Folder 3)
      - This Week, 1991 (Box 198, Folder 4)
      - Tort Reform, 1986 (Box 198, Folder 5)
      - Women in Medicine Project, 1986-1991 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - American Medical Association/American Academy of Allergy and Immunology Membership Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 184, Folder 3-4)
    - American Medical Student Association, 1997 (Box 520, Folder 25)
    - American Medical Writers Association, 1981-1986 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - American Psychiatric Association, 1992 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - American Public Health Association, 1995 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - American Rheumatism Association, 1982-1993 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - American Society of Addiction Medicine, 1991 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - American Society of Association Executives, 1988-1990 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - American Society of Internal Medicine
      - 1987 (Box 198, Folder 13-14)
      - 1988 (Box 198, Folder 15)
      - 1989 (Box 199, Folder 1)
      - 1990 (Box 199, Folder 2-3)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 257, Folder 7)
      - 1993 (Box 257, Folder 8)
      - 1994 (Box 199, Folder 4)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - American Society of Nephrology, 1993 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - American Society of Plastic and Reconstructive Surgeons
      - 1989 (Box 199, Folder 7)
      - 1992 (Box 199, Folder 8)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - American Thoracic Society
      - 1987-1989 (Box 199, Folder 10)
      - 1992-1995 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Americans for Responsible Reform, 1994 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Ansell Medical, 1992 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Association for Respiratory Health of Minorities, 1992-1993 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Association for the Care of Asthma, 1988 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges
      - 1988 (Box 200, Folder 2-3)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 200, Folder 4)
      - 1991 (Box 200, Folder 5)
      - 1992 (Box 200, Folder 6-7)
      - 1993 (Box 200, Folder 8)
      - 1994 (Box 201, Folder 1-2)
      - 1995 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Association of Professors of Medicine, 1987-1988 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Association of Subspecialty Professors, 1993 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Association of Trial Lawyers of America, 1990-1991 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Asthma and Allergy Foundation of America
      - 1976-1978 (Box 201, Folder 9)
      - 1979-1983 (Box 202, Folder 1-7)
      - 1986 (Box 257, Folder 9)
      - 1987, 1991 (Box 258, Folder 1-3)
      - Advance
        - 1983-1988 (Box 202, Folder 8)
        - 1989 (Box 203, Folder 1)
        - 1990-1992, 2001 (Box 203, Folder 2)
      - Agenda Book, 1983 (Box 446, Folder 14)
      - American College of Allergists Relations, 1985-1986 (Box 203, Folder 5)
      - American Legion Film Project, 1983 (Box 203, Folder 6)
      - Asthma and Allergy Awareness Month, 1987-1988 (Box 203, Folder 10)
      - Asthma and Allergy Awareness Week, 1979-1986 (Box 203, Folder 7-9)
      - Asthma and Allergy Exchange
        - 1997-1998 (Box 490, Folder 11)
        - 1997 (Box 495, Folder 4)
      - Asthma and Allergy Hotline, 1987 (Box 203, Folder 11)
      - Asthma and Schools Video, 1987 (Box 203, Folder 12)
      - Asthma Athlete of the Year, 1986 (Box 203, Folder 13)
      - Asthma Care Training Program, 1986-1987 (Box 204, Folder 1)
      - Big Apple Blossom Ball, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 2)
      - Blanks and Forms, 1987-1990 (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Board Meeting Minutes and Reports, 1982-1990 (Box 204, Folder 3)
      - Brochure Revision Project, 1987-1991 (Box 204, Folder 4)
      - Chapter Development, 1984-1986 (Box 204, Folder 5)
      - Chapters
        - 1985-1987 (Box 204, Folder 6)
        - 1988-1990 (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Consumer Advisory, 1985 (Box 204, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence
        - 1982-1986 (Box 204, Folder 8-10)
        - 1987, 1989 (Box 258, Folder 6-7)
        - 1988, 1990-1995 (Box 205, Folder 2-6)
        - 1996-2001 (Box 670, Folder 3)
      - Costs/Inventory, 1988-1991 (Box 258, Folder 8)
      - A Critical Appraisal of Current Diagnostic and Therapeutical Techniques for Common Allergic Diseases, 1985 (Box 205, Folder 7)
      - Developing Investigator Awards, 1987 (Box 205, Folder 8)
      - Document of Reasoned Judgment, 1985 (Box 205, Folder 9)
      - Fall Meeting, 1982 (Box 205, Folder 10)
      - Fellowship Grants, 1983-1986 (Box 206, Folder 1)
      - Financial Oversight Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 206, Folder 2)
      - Funding Appeal, 1984-1985 (Box 206, Folder 3)
      - Greater Cincinnati Chapter, 1985-1986 (Box 206, Folder 4)
      - Income Statements, 1987 (Box 206, Folder 5)
      - Information Clearinghouse Service, 1983-1984 (Box 206, Folder 6)
      - Informational packet, 1983 (Box 446, Folder 15)
      - Medical-Scientific Council, 1983-1989 (Box 206, Folder 7)
      - Memorials, John Ratajczyk, 1983 (Box 206, Folder 8)
      - Orchids to You Campaign, 1987 (Box 206, Folder 9)
      - Pamphlets, undated (Box 455, Folder 22)
      - Patient Education Inventory, 1985-1987 (Box 206, Folder 10)
      - Patient Letter Volunteers, 1988-1991 (Box 206, Folder 11)
      - Physicians Referral Service, 1986 (Box 206, Folder 12)
      - Position Statement Handbook, 1985 (Box 206, Folder 13)
      - Poster Child, 1985-1988 (Box 206, Folder 14)
      - Press Packet for Science Writers Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 206, Folder 15)
      - Public Policy Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 206, Folder 16)
      - Public Service Announcements, 1984 (Box 206, Folder 17)
      - Related Organization Correspondence, 1983 (Box 206, Folder 18)
      - Report to Executive Committee
        - 1985 (Box 206, Folder 19)
        - 1986, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 1-3)
      - Reports, 1988-1992 (Box 258, Folder 9)
      - Retreat, 1985 (Box 207, Folder 4)
      - Riverboat Cruise, 1988-1989 (Box 207, Folder 5)
      - St. Elsewhere Benefit, 1987-1988 (Box 207, Folder 6)
      - Schering Asthma Videotape, 1984 (Box 207, Folder 7)
      - Sneeze and Wheeze of Asthma and Allergies, 1985 (Box 455, Folder 21)
      - Tribute to Sheldon Siegel, Program, 1985 (Box 446, Folder 16)
      - Twelfth Night Ball, 1984-1985 (Box 207, Folder 8)
      - Unproven Techniques, 1984 (Box 207, Folder 9)
      - Usted Puede Controlar el Asma: un Libro para la Familia, 1998 (Box 492, Folder 5)
      - Usted Puede Controlar el Asma: un Libro para Niños, 1998 (Box 492, Folder 7)
      - Washington Reports, 1983-1985 (Box 207, Folder 10)
      - Wisconsin Chapter, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 11)
      - Wisconsin Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 207, Folder 12)
      - Wisconsin Chapter, 1984 (Box 207, Folder 13)
      - Wisconsin Chapter, 1987-1991 (Box 207, Folder 14)
      - Wisconsin Chapter, Development Committee, 1987-1995 (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - Wisconsin Chapter, Sample Book, 1988 (Box 208, Folder 2)
      - You Can Control Asthma: A Book for Kids, 1998 (Box 492, Folder 6)
      - You Can Control Asthma: A Book for the Family, 1998 (Box 492, Folder 4)
    - Asthma and Allergy Foundation of America/American Academy of Allergy and Immunology Film Project, 1983-1984 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Asthma and Allergy Foundation of America/American Academy of Allergy and Immunology Task Force, 1993 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Asthma and Allergy Hospital of America, 1987 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Asthma Care Trust, 1985 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Asthma Education and Resource Council, Connections, 2000 (Box 520, Folder 21)
    - Asthma Education and Resource Council of Marin (CA), Organizational Scrapbook, 1996 (Box 446, Folder 17)
    - Asthma Foundation of the Philippines, 1991 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Asthma Outcomes Monitoring System Baseline Psychometric Report (JCAAI), April 1998 (Box 675, Folder 6)
    - Asthma Zero Mortality Alliance, 1993 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Asthma Zero Mortality Coalition (Alliance), 1993-1994 (Box 670, Folder 4-5)
    - Astra USA, 1994 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Aventis, 2000-2001 (Box 540, Folder 9)
    - Axonics, 1986 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Becton Dickinson Company, 1990 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Beecham Laboratories, 1985 (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - BioSearch, 1988 (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield Association, 1986 (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - Boehringer Ingelheim, 1984-1989 (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - Broadcast Music, Inc., 1990 (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Burroughs Wellcome, 1986-1990 (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - Burroughs Wellcome Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 208, Folder 16)
    - Burroughs Wellcome Fund Developing Investigator Award, undated (Box 446, Folder 18)
    - Business and Health, Managing Asthma Care, 1995 (Box 446, Folder 19)
    - Canadian Pediatric Society, 1983-1986 (Box 208, Folder 17)
    - Canadian Society of Allergy and Clinical Immunology, 1988-1993 (Box 208, Folder 18)
    - Cancer Research Institute, 1994 (Box 208, Folder 19)
    - Center for Medical Communications, 1990 (Box 208, Folder 20)
    - Center for Science in the Public Interest, 1987 (Box 208, Folder 21)
    - Center Laboratories, 1985-1988 (Box 208, Folder 22)
    - Child Health Research Center, 1992 (Box 208, Folder 23)
    - Childhood Asthma Management Program, 1999 (Box 520, Folder 17)
    - CIBA Pharmaceuticals, 1953-1959 (Box 446, Folder 20)
    - Cliggott Communications, 1990-1991 (Box 208, Folder 24)
    - Clinical Immunology Society/American Academy of Allergy and Immunology Joint Meeting, 1993 (Box 208, Folder 25)
    - Coalition for Equal Access to Medicine, 1993 (Box 208, Folder 26)
    - Coalition on Smoking or Health
      - 1985 (Box 258, Folder 10)
      - 1986-1994 (Box 258, Folder 11)
    - Coca-Cola, 1985 (Box 208, Folder 27)
    - College of American Pathologists, 1982-1992 (Box 208, Folder 28)
    - Congress of California Dermatological Societies, 1990 (Box 208, Folder 29)
    - Consortium on Children's Asthma Camps, 1994-1996 (Box 208, Folder 30)
    - Consumer Update on Allergy, Allergy and Asthma Network/Mothers of Asthmatics, 1994 (Box 446, Folder 21)
    - Council for International Organizations of Medical Sciences, 1993 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Council of Academic Societies, 1986-1990 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Council of Academic Societies, 1991-1995 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Council of Medical Specialty Societies
      - 1984-1986 (Box 209, Folder 4-9)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 210, Folder 1-6)
      - 1989-1993 (Box 211, Folder 1-27)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 259, Folder 1-4)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 212, Folder 1-5)
      - 1995 (Box 213, Folder 1-2)
      - Annual Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 213, Folder 3-6)
      - Correspondence
        - 1987 (Box 259, Folder 5-7)
        - 1987 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Spring Meeting, 1995 (Box 213, Folder 7)
      - Winter Meeting, 1992-1993 (Box 213, Folder 8-9)
    - Council of State, Regional and Local Allergy Societies, Minutes and Meeting Rosters, 1973-1977 (Box 446, Folder 22)
    - Council of Subspecialty Societies
      - 1984-1995 (Box 214, Folder 1-6)
    - Council on Graduate Medical Education
      - 1991-1994 (Box 214, Folder 7-8)
    - Criep Lectureship Fund, 1979-1983 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Current Issues in Allergy and Immunology, 1991-1994 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Department of Health and Human Services, Public Health Service, 1987-1996 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Department of Justice, Anti-Trust Division, 1987 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Dow Chemical Company, 1988-1995 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Ear, Nose, and Throat Societies, 1980-1988 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Enviracaire, 1988 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1988-1992 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - European Academy of Allergology and Clinical Immunology
      - 1982-1995 (Box 215, Folder 7-9)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1982-1986, 1988 (Box 215, Folder 10-11)
    - Federated Council of Internal Medicine, 1994 (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology, 1988-1996 (Box 215, Folder 13)
    - Federation of Regional, State and Local Allergy Societies, 2000 (Box 455, Folder 23)
    - Fisons Corporation, 1983-1994 (Box 215, Folder 14-15)
    - Food Allergy Network
      - 1992-1996 (Box 216, Folder 1-4)
      - 1997-2000 (Box 543, Folder 21)
    - Food and Drug Administration
      - Allergenic Products Advisory Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Aspartame, 1986-1987 (Box 216, Folder 8)
      - Benedryl, 1985 (Box 216, Folder 9)
      - Conference on Fraud, 1986 (Box 216, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence
        - Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 216, Folder 11-12)
        - Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 217, Folder 1-7)
      - Discussions, 1984-1986 (Box 217, Folder 8)
      - Draft Guidelines for Clinical Trials, 1985 (Box 217, Folder 9)
      - Hismanal, 1992 (Box 217, Folder 10)
      - Ingredient Labeling of Foods, 1985-1987 (Box 217, Folder 11)
      - Investigational Drugs, 1987 (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Methacholine, 1985 (Box 218, Folder 2)
      - Office of Consumer Affairs, 1986-1988 (Box 218, Folder 3)
      - Over-the-Counter Drug Labeling, 1986 (Box 218, Folder 4)